[
  {
    "question": "1 x 8",
    "options": ["6", "8", "10"],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 x 8",
    "options": ["12", "14", "16"],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 x 8",
    "options": ["18", "21", "24"],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 x 8",
    "options": ["28", "32", "36"],
    "correctAnswer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 x 8",
    "options": ["35", "40", "45"],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 x 8",
    "options": ["42", "48", "54"],
    "correctAnswer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 x 8",
    "options": ["49", "56", "63"],
    "correctAnswer": "56"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 x 8",
    "options": ["56", "64", "72"],
    "correctAnswer": "64"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 x 8",
    "options": ["63", "72", "81"],
    "correctAnswer": "72"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 8",
    "options": ["70", "80", "90"],
    "correctAnswer": "80"
  }
]
